http://www.sugar.ca/terms-of-use

About UsAbout UsOur TeamStrategic PrioritiesNutrition Information ServiceNutrition and Academic AdvisorsTrade AlliancesSugar BasicsSugar BasicsCarbohydrate and Sugars TerminologyTypes of SugarSources of SugarGeography of SugarPurification of SugarRoles Sugar Plays in FoodsUncover the Truth About SugarUncover the Truth About SugarBehaviourDental HealthDiabetesNutritional ValueOverweight and ObesityPhysical ActivityTest your Sugar IQSugars Consumption & GuidelinesSugars Consumption & GuidelinesConsumption of Sugars in CanadaDietary Guidelines on SugarsNutrition Labelling and ClaimsSugars & HealthSugars & HealthCarbohydrate Digestion and AbsorptionAppetite and Food IntakeCancerCardiovascular DiseaseCognitionDental HealthType 2 DiabetesLiver HealthOverweight and ObesityPhysical ActivitySugar Science & ResearchSugar Science & ResearchCSI Collaborative ResearchLatest Sugars-Related Research (2020)Latest Sugars-Related Research (2020)Sugars Research 2019Scientific ReferencesResourcesResourcesResources to Order or DownloadResources to Order or DownloadOrder FormCSI Recipe CollectionTest Your Sugar IQInternational TradeInternational TradeCanadian Sugar MarketCanadian Sugar MarketCanadian Sugar TodayCanadian Sugar ManufacturersHistory of the Sugar Industry in CanadaRationalization and ReinvestmentValue of Sugar to the Canadian EconomyCanadian Sugar Industry StatisticsCanada's Open Market Sugar PolicyGlobal Sugar Trade (WTO)North American TradeRegional and Bilateral TradeTrade LinksWhat’s NewWhat’s NewCarbohydrate Nutrition NewsInternational Trade News
Home
Contact
Contact Us
Français
About UsOur TeamStrategic PrioritiesNutrition Information ServiceNutrition and Academic AdvisorsTrade AlliancesSugar BasicsCarbohydrate and Sugars TerminologyTypes of SugarSources of SugarGeography of SugarPurification of SugarRoles Sugar Plays in FoodsUncover the Truth About SugarTest your Sugar IQSugars Consumption & GuidelinesConsumption of Sugars in CanadaDietary Guidelines on SugarsNutrition Labelling and ClaimsSugars & HealthCarbohydrate Digestion and AbsorptionAppetite and Food IntakeCancerCardiovascular DiseaseCognitionDental HealthType 2 DiabetesLiver HealthOverweight and ObesityPhysical ActivitySugar Science & ResearchCSI Collaborative ResearchLatest Sugars-Related Research (2020)Scientific ReferencesResourcesResources to Order or DownloadCSI Recipe CollectionTest Your Sugar IQInternational TradeCanadian Sugar MarketCanada's Open Market Sugar PolicyGlobal Sugar Trade (WTO)North American TradeRegional and Bilateral TradeTrade LinksWhat’s NewCarbohydrate Nutrition NewsInternational Trade News
What's New
November 30, 2020
- International Trade News
The Global Sugar Alliance has Called on India to Drop its Controversial Sugar Subsidies
November 21, 2020
- International Trade News
Agri-food Exporters Say Canada Needs a Permanent Free Trade Agreement with the UK
Terms of Use
Please read this Agreement carefully before using this website www.sugar.ca or any associated sites, including any tools, forums or educational resources (the “Web Site”). It is an agreement between users of the Web Site and Canadian Sugar Institute (“CSI”) and governs the access to and the use of this Web Site. It contains liability exclusions and limitations and other important provisions. By accessing and using this Web Site, you acknowledge and signify that you have read, understood, and agreed to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree with all of the provisions of this agreement, you may not use this Web Site.
Your acceptance of this agreement
This Web Site Use Agreement (referred to below as the “Agreement”) governs the access to and the use of the Web Site and constitutes an agreement between CSI (referred to below as “CSI”, “we”, “us” or “our”) and users of this Web Site, such as you. Each time you use the Web Site, you signify your acceptance and agreement, and the acceptance and agreement of any party you purport to represent, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Agreement as it may be amended from time to time. By using this Web Site you also represent and warrant that you have the legal authority to agree to and accept this Agreement on behalf of yourself and any party you purport to represent. If you do not agree with all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement, or you are not authorized to agree to and accept this Agreement, you may not use this Web Site.
Changes to this agreement
CSI may amend this Agreement at any time and from time to time without notice to you by updating this posting. By continuing to use this Web Site or any portion thereof after the amendment is posted, you will signify your acceptance and agreement, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by the Agreement as amended. You should therefore review this Agreement periodically for changes. If you do not agree with the amendments to this Agreement, you may not use this Web Site.
Ownership permitted use of the web site and its content
All CSI Content contained on this Web Site is the property of Canadian Sugar Institute or its licensors as the case may be, and is protected by Canadian and international copyright, trademark, and other applicable laws. For the purposes of this Agreement, “CSI Content” includes any and all material, information in text, graphical, video and audio forms, images, reports, articles, publications, data, databases, charts, graphics, photographs, illustrations, maps, interfaces, web pages, text, files, software, product names, company names, trade-marks, logos and trade names contained on this Web Site, other than User Content (as defined below), as well as the manner in which the Content is presented or appears and all information relating thereto.
Permitted Uses
CSI hereby grants you a personal, limited, revocable, non-transferable and non-exclusive license to access, read, download the Content located on this Web Site for personal, non-commercial and not-for-profit use only. The Web Site is made available to you for your lawful, personal use only.
You may print pages from the Web Site for your personal, non-commercial use only, provided that you do not modify any of the Content and you do not remove or alter any visible or non-visible identification, marks, notices, or disclaimers. Other than as specifically described herein, the Web Site and its Content may not be copied, imitated, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, modified, indexed, catalogued, merged with other data, mirrored or distributed in any way, in whole or in part, without the express prior written consent of CSI.
Prohibited Uses
You may not, and may not allow others to, directly or indirectly: (i) use the Website and/or the Content for any purpose not expressly permitted by this Agreement; (ii) remove from any copy of the Content, the copyright or other proprietary notices contained in the Content; (iii) sell, modify or attempt to modify the Content in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform or distribute or otherwise use any Content for any public, commercial or non-personal purpose, including, without limitation, use of the Content on any other website; (iv) use the Web Site in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, impair, interfere with the security of, negatively affect the functioning of, or otherwise abuse the Web Site or any part thereof, or any services, system resources, accounts, servers, networks, affiliated or linked sites connected to or accessible through the Web Site; (v) disrupt or interfere with any other person’s use or enjoyment of the Web Site or any affiliated or linked sites, or any services thereof; (vi) use any software which is used in the operation of the Web Site or any part thereof, except while you are browsing the Web Site or performing other activities provided through the Web Site, as applicable and as permitted; (vii) copy any of the software used at Web Site unless expressly permitted to do so by CSI; and/or (viii) copy or imitate, in whole or in part, the design of the Web Site or any part thereof.
Trademark Information
CANADIAN SUGAR INSTITUTE and CANADIAN SUGAR INSTTITUTE & Design, and other marks and logos appearing on the Web Site are registered and unregistered trade-marks or trade names of CSI. Other product and company names and logos appearing on the Web Site may be registered or unregistered trade-names or trade marks of their respective owners. Any use of the trademarks, trade names and logos (collectively the “Marks”) displayed on this Web Site, except as expressly provided in this Agreement, is strictly prohibited. Nothing appearing on this Web Site or elsewhere shall be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use, display or copy, in any manner, any Mark displayed on this Web Site.
No Advice
This Web Site and the Content have been independently researched, written and reviewed by CSI or others. Some content may be based on scientific evidence. The Content is for reference, educational, informational or demonstrative purposes only and may not be relied upon as professional, investment, legal, accounting, tax, health, medical or other advice or a substitute for such advice, or, in the case of health-related information, a medical diagnosis, or a treatment from a physician or qualified healthcare professional. You are responsible for obtaining appropriate advice from qualified external sources prior to acting upon any information available at or through this Web Site.
Privacy Policy
CSI may, in its discretion, monitor your use of the Web Site or any part thereof. CSI collects, uses and discloses personal information in accordance with its Privacy Policy, which is incorporated by reference into this Agreement and available by clicking here. This Privacy Policy may be amended by CSI from time to time, in its sole discretion, without notifying or being liable to you or any other person, by making an amended Privacy Policy accessible through the Web Site. Each time you use the Web Site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by CSI in accordance with the Privacy Policy as it then reads.
Other Sites
While the Web Site may contain links to third party sites (“Linked Sites”), CSI is not responsible for the content of any Linked Sites. CSI provides links to Linked Sites as a convenience only. CSI makes no representation or warranty regarding any Linked Sites or their content, and does not endorse any Linked Sites or any information, or products or services appearing, available or described thereon. Links to Linked Sites do not imply that CSI sponsors, endorses, is affiliated or associated with, the Linked Sites or their associated companies or products, or is legally authorized to use any content displayed in or accessed through the links to the Linked Sites. When you access such Linked Sites, you are doing so at your own risk and are subject to the terms and conditions of use of the Linked Sites in question.
Disclaimers
Your use of the web site or any part thereof is at your own risk. the web site and its content are provided on an “as is” basis, and without any representations, warranties or conditions of any kind, whether express or implied, including without limitation representations, warranties or conditions of or relating to uninterrupted or error free operation, freedom from viruses, trojan horses, worms or other destructive or disruptive components, availability, accuracy, veracity, completeness, currentness, reliability, timeliness, legality, suitability, privacy, security, merchantability, quality, title, non-infringement, or fitness for a particular purpose, or those arising out of a course of dealing or usage of trade, all of which are hereby disclaimed by CSI to the fullest extent permitted by law.
You (and not CSI) assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair or correction to any equipment arising from or connected to your access to the web site.
Liability Limitations
In no event will CSI, its licensors, suppliers, service providers or their respective directors, officers or employees, be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, punitive and exemplary damages or losses, howsoever caused, arising from, connected with, or relating to the web site or any part thereof, including, without limitation, access to and use of the web site or any part thereof, access to and use of any CSI forums, educational resources or tools, or this agreement including but not limited to, damages for loss of use, lost profits or lost savings, or resulting from viruses, data corruption, failed messages, transmission errors or problems, links to third-party websites, third-party content, user content, products or services, the use or inability to use this website or the content under any theory of liability (whether on a contractual or extracontractual basis, tort, strict liability or any other theory or law or equity), regardless of any negligence or other fault or wrongdoing and fundamental breach by CSI or any person for whom CSI is responsible, even if CSI or its licensors, suppliers, service providers or their respective directors, officers or employees have been advised of the possibility of such damages or claim.
CSI is not responsible for any content that you may find undesirable or objectionable.
Indemnity
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless CSI and all of its agents, directors, employees, information providers, licensors and licensees, officers and all other related, associated, or connected individual or corporate parties (collectively, the “Indemnified Parties”) from and against any and all actions, proceedings, costs, claims damages, demands, liabilities and costs, including without limitation reasonable legal fees and expenses, sustained and/or incurred by the Indemnified Parties, directly or indirectly arising out of or connected to your use of the Web Site or the Content in breach of this Agreement, your violation or infringement of the rights of others, and/or your violation of any applicable laws. You will assist and co-operate as fully as reasonably required by CSI in the defence of any such claim or demand.
Linking and Framing
Links to this Web Site without the express written permission of CSI are strictly prohibited. To request permission to link to the Web Site, please contact CSI at info@sugar.ca. CSI reserves the right to summarily cancel and revoke at any time and without notice any permission it may give to link to this Web Site.
Jurisdictional Issues
This Web Site is controlled by CSI from its offices in Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Access to this Web Site from locations where the Content is illegal is prohibited. If you are accessing this Web Site from other locations, you must comply with all laws applicable in your jurisdiction.
Termination of web site use and this agreement
If you breach any provision of this Agreement, CSI may prohibit you from accessing or using the Web Site, any CSI Forums, Educational Resources or Tools. CSI may, at any time without notice or liability, and for any reason whatsoever, terminate, change, suspend or discontinue any aspect of the Web Site and/or any part thereof, including i) changing the availability of, restricting access to, or imposing limits on any or all features or services on, or links to, the Web Site; ii) removing, adding, modifying or otherwise changing any Content on the Web Site. CSI reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to correct any errors or omissions in any portion of the Web Site at any time without notice, but confirms that it has no obligation to do so.
If this Agreement or your permission to use the Web Site is terminated by you or us for any reason, then (a) you must cease your use of this Web Site and destroy all materials obtained from this Web Site and all related documentation and all copies and installations thereof, whether made under this Agreement or otherwise; (b) this Agreement will nevertheless continue to apply and be binding upon you in respect of your prior use of the Web Site and anything connected with, relating to or arising from that use; and (c) we may continue to use and disclose your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. Sections 3 (Ownership), 4 (Permitted Uses), 5 (Prohibited Uses), 6 (Trademark Information), 8 (Privacy Policy), 9 (Other Sites), 10 (Disclaimers), 11 (Liability Limitations), 12 (Indemnity), 13 (Linking and Framing), 15 (Termination), 16 (Governing Law and Dispute Resolution) and 17 (Contact) survive indefinitely after the termination of this Agreement.
Governing law and dispute resolution
This Agreement, your use of this Web Site and its Content, and all matters relating thereto are governed by the laws of the Province of Ontario, Canada and the federal laws of Canada, excluding any rules of private international law or the conflict of laws which would lead to the application of any other laws.
Any dispute between CSI and you arising from or relating to this Web Site or the Content or this Agreement shall be resolved before the Courts of the Ottawa, Canada sitting in the City of Ottawa, and you hereby irrevocably submit to the original and exclusive jurisdiction of those Courts in respect of any such dispute.
Contact Us
If you have any comments or questions about this Agreement or your use of the Web Site or any part thereof, please contact CSI at:
10 Bay Street, Suite 620
Toronto, Ontario
M5J 2R8
Canada
Telephone: 416-368-8091
Fax: 416-368-6426
Email: info@sugar.ca
General
If any provision of this Agreement is found to be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed to be severable from the rest of the Agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.
No waiver by either party of any breach of or default under this Agreement shall be deemed to be a waiver of any preceding or subsequent breach or default.
This Agreement, including any changes made to this Agreement from time to time, constitutes the entire agreement between you and CSI relating to your use of the Web Site and supersedes all previous agreements, written, oral or otherwise, between the you and CSI with respect to your use of the Web Site and the Content. This Agreement does not vary, alter, modify or otherwise affect any other more specific agreements between you and CSI regarding other matters.
Any rights not expressly granted by this Agreement are reserved to CSI.
About Us
Our TeamStrategic PrioritiesNutrition Information ServiceNutrition and Academic AdvisorsTrade Alliances
Sugar Basics
Carbohydrate and Sugars TerminologyTypes of SugarSources of SugarGeography of SugarPurification of SugarRoles Sugar Plays in FoodsUncover the Truth About SugarTest your Sugar IQ
Sugars Consumption & Guidelines
Consumption of Sugars in CanadaDietary Guidelines on SugarsNutrition Labelling and Claims
Sugars & Health
Carbohydrate Digestion and AbsorptionAppetite and Food IntakeCancerCardiovascular DiseaseCognitionDental HealthType 2 DiabetesLiver HealthOverweight and ObesityPhysical Activity
Sugar Science & Research
CSI Collaborative ResearchLatest Sugars-Related Research (2020)Scientific References
Resources
Resources to Order or DownloadCSI Recipe CollectionTest Your Sugar IQ
International Trade
Canadian Sugar MarketCanada's Open Market Sugar PolicyGlobal Sugar Trade (WTO)North American TradeRegional and Bilateral TradeTrade Links
